Guide to the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, General Committee of the New York Central Railroad (Lines West), chairman's files, 1909-1962 [bulk 1931-1962].
Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, General Committee of the New York Central Railroad (Lines West), chairman's files, 1909-1962 [bulk 1931-1962].
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, General Committee of the New York Central Railroad (Lines West), chairman's files,
1909-1962 [bulk 1931-1962].
5182
Doble, William J., 1904-1972.
16 linear ft.
Correspondence, reports, agreements, press releases, circulars, publications, decisions.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Files of the chairman of the New York Central Railroad (Lines West) of the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, including information regarding labor relations on the Michigan Central, Peoria and Eastern, and Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroads.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
William Doble was born October 25, 1904, in Exeter, Devon, England. He immigrated to the U.S. and found employment in the railroad industry. Doble was a member of the Blue Mason Lodge and the OPA Advisory Committee.
Doble joined the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalman of America in 1924. With only an elementary school education he rose through the ranks to the position of chief signalman and ultimately became General Chairman of the Brotherhood, for New York Central, Lines West. His jurisdiction extended to local unions of the Big Four, the Michigan Central Railroad, the New York Central Railroad, the Peoria and Eastern Railway, and, Foreman and Inspector of the Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad. He served in the office of General Chairman from 1931 to 1962 (as far as could be discerned from the collection). From his desk in Ferndale, Michigan, he handled grievances and channeled labor-management relations. Doble functioned as the coordinator of subordinate locals' activities, grievance claims, and disputes concerning conditions of employment.
The railroad signal department performs the vital functions of expediting and controlling traffic while maintaining safe conditions. It represents one of the most responsible and sensitive units of the entire railroad system. Signalmen are directly Involved with expanding the mileage of protected track, and modernizing existing railroad plants. Their activities necessitate smooth coordination with other units of the system to insure maximum safety and efficiency.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The original order of the files has been maintained wherever possible. The numbers are not always consecutive due to missing files.
The collection consists of Doble's personal and professional files. It is largely composed of agreements and correspondence between union officials and local members and grievance chairmen, N.R.A.B. cases and other pertinent to railroading in general and to signalmen. Overall, the files reveal the process and function of the union hierarchy and general principles of union organization. The contents make evident certain achievements and benefits for the workers and the industry which have contributed to the fostering of harmonious Industrial relations.
Materials on the St. Lawrence Seaway Project (1941-1952) include press releases; letters regarding opposition of railroad labor to the St. Lawrence Seaway Project (1952); circulars from Tom J. McGrath (executive director, National St. Lawrence Project Conference, a nationwide organization in opposition to the St. Lawrence Seaway Project); and papers and publications on the proposed project and its effects.
Also included are a report of the proceedings of the General System Committee meetings of the New York Central lines; by-laws of the General Committee of the New York Central Railroad (Lines West) of the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen (BRS) (1931); amalgamation of various lines of the New York Central system (1931); proposed by-laws and general rules of the General Grievance Committee of New York Central lines, BRS; minutes of meetings of New York Central lines (1927); reports of the secretary-treasurer, New York Central (Lines West) (1929-1960); financial statements of the General System Committee (1933-1952); minutes of meetings of the general chairman and BRS officers (1944-1960); conference (with by-laws) for the formation of a co-operative association of general chairmen representing the standard railroad labor organizations on the New York Central system lines (1932); circular letters (1952-1956) from the office of General Chairman Doble regarding protection of men working on highway crossings (1953); union shop operations (1956); recall of men laid off during the steel strike; and reports of Doble (1934-1946).
Other matters include the question of whether Canadian employees working for the Michigan Central Railroad in Canada are subject to the provisions of railroad unemployment insurance (1938); settlement of work claims (1954-1955); letters regarding BRS conducting an organizing campaign among signal department employees on the New York Central system and its request to represent signal foremen and inspectors; files on organizing by the American Railway Supervisors' Association; minutes of general chairmen and local chairmen of the New York Central System (1929); and decisions of the 40-Hour Week Committee on revision of make-up time rules, traveling time, starting time, Sunday and holiday pay, day's work and overtime, reduction in force rules, stand-by rules, bulletin rules, and shift rules.
Materials on overtime and consolidations (1930-1961) include letters regarding Council Order No. 8682 declaring six holidays per year for the duration of World War II (1942); a strike of locomotive engineers, firemen and conductors on the New York Central system (Lines West), Michigan Central railroad, and the Big Four Railroads (1952); rights of promoted men when their positions are abolished (1952); and participation in the joint 1961 wage and rules movement for a general wage increase; numerous other routine matters regarding individual grievances, clauses in contracts and government regulations.
Additional materials (1936-1958) include letters regarding work week, equal distribution of employment, an official strike ballot regarding wage requests of 1942; Railway Labor Executives' Association resolution, statements, and reports dealing with employment of war prisoners on the railroads (1942); correspondence regarding the Pennsylvania-New York Central Railroad merger (1962); record books of BRS expenses (1937-1952); a memorandum relating to "certain" Chinese railway engineers training for railroad service (1944); and New York Central lines regulations and requirements governing employee physical examinations and re-examinations upon promotion (1933-1948); apprenticeship training in the signal department (1947-1956); regulations governing the issuance of free or reduced rate transportation (1942); a record book (1936) of BRS Grand Lodge dues for various locals (1936); and minutes and proceedings of the 1958 BRS convention.
The significant correspondence in this accession was generated by Doble, and by C.K. Fields (vice-president, legislative representative), J.M. Pattee (general chairman); W.E. Aurand (general secretary-treasurer), A.E. Lyon (grand president), D.W. Helt (grand president) Jesse Clark (president) and local officers of the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen. Other correspondents include officers and employees of the Association of General Chairmen, New York Central; the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes; the Michigan Central Railroad; the New York Central Railroad; the Peoria and Eastern Railroad; and the Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad.
Doble, William J.,; Humphrey, Hubert H. (Hubert Horatio), 1911-1978.; Benefit Association Railway Employees.; Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees.; Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen.; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers.; Lake Erie and Eastern Railroad.; Michigan Central Railroad.; New York Central Railroad.; Peoria and Eastern Railroad.; Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company.; Railway Labor's Political League.; St. Lawrence Seaway Development Corporation.; United States. National Railroad Adjustment Board.; United States.; Color blindness--United States.; Labor laws and legislation--United States.; Liability for railroad accidents--United States.; Prisoners of war--United States.; Railroads--United States--Abandonment.; Railroads--United States--Consolidation.; Trade-unions--United States--Political activity.; Railroad employees; Railroad signalmen
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
CONTAINER LIST
- 1-1. Work Jurisdiction.
  Materials on work jurisdiction (1931-1957) include correspondence (1933-1957) regarding workers other than signalmen performing signal work (i.e., electricians of the equipment department, section men, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, maintenance of way shop employees, bridge and building department forces, Western Union Telegraph Company, communications department); seniority rights in both the transportation and signal department; and letters regarding carrier violations in the observance of craft lines as defined in the scope rules of the signalmen's agreement, and the contracting out of signal work.
  - Elkhart Signal Shop Work (1931-45) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Painting of Signal Apparatus (1943-45) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cincinnati Northern RR (1935-45) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Installation of Relay Houses - N.Y. Central (1940-41) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Shipley vs. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie RR Company (1949) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Maume River Bridge, Toledo, Ohio (1946) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - C.R. Interlocking Plant, Chicago (1941) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Western Union (1944-46) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Shop Crafts Agreement (1931) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - National Mediation Board - Representation of Employees (1945) NY Central RR (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Order of Railroad Telegraphers (ORT) (1940) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Local 35, Doughton, Ohio (1935) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Adjustment of Pay - Michigan Central (1942) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - ORT (1939) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - ORT, Monroe, Michigan (1937) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Michigan Central Railroad (1934-37) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Machinist (1937) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - M of W, Illinois (1940) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Pay Adjustment P and E Railroad (1941) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - San Francisco Trades Council vs. General Railway Signal Company (1938) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - ORT (1938) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Senate Bill 74 (1937-38). Roster of Senate and House of Representatives (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Local 35 - Maintenance (1943) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - C.N.R.R. (1939) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Sheet Metal Workers (1950) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - National Railroad Adjustment Board, 3rd Division (pamphlets) Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees (1930) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Communications Department (1950) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Grand Lodge Agreement (1947) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - M of W and Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad Company (1950) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - N.R.A.B., 3rd Division - Reading Company (1946 - 50) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - N.R.A.B. - M of W - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation (1950) M of W agreements (1950) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - N.Y. Central Lines West - B.R.S. of A, agreement (1950) - Train banners (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - M.C.R.R. (1931) (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - I.B.E.W. (1945) (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - I.B.E.W. (1951-56) (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - N.R.A.B. (1951) Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Company (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Local 4l (1950 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Rules 140 and 141 for Electrical Workers (1951) (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Local 10 (1951) (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Scope of Work (1952) (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - O.R.T. (1951-53) (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Crossing Gates - Repairs (1941) (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - N.Y.C. System - I.B.E.W. (1953) (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - N.Y.C. System - I.B.E.W. (1953) (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - I.B.E.W. Work Rules (1953-55) (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - B.R.S. of A. Michigan (1956) (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Jesse Clark (1957) (Box 1, Folder 52)
- 1-3. Legal Aid.
  Materials on the Legal Aid Department (1932) established for the purpose of advising injured members and dependents of those who died as the result of injuries regarding their legal rights and remedies under the Federal Employers' Liability Act; also include rules and regulations of the legal aid service of the Brotherhood.
  - Employers Liability Act 1932-47 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Legal Aid Service (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1-5. Color Perception.
  Materials on color perception (1935-1945) include letters regarding an employee being disqualified for being unable to meet visual acuity standards, an employee removed from his position because of defective color perception, and demotion because of alleged color blindness.
  - L. Hox on disqualification due to color test failure (1939) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Vision regulations (1937) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Demotion of D. Hunsinger Due to poor color perception (1935-36) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Demotion of Kubsh - Defective color perception (1937-39) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - P and LE Ortho-Rater (1949) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Copy article on color vision (1951) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 1-6. Meal Periods.
  - Missing (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Rule 12" - Interpretation (1938) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Claims by workers for overtime pay (1934-35) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1-7. Political Legislation.
  Materials on political legislation (1946-1949) include a copy of HR.3020 to amend the National Labor Relations Act to provide additional facilities for the mediation of labor disputes affecting commerce, and to equalize legal responsibilities of labor organizations and employers; copy of HR.2536 to amend the Interstate Commerce Act (1946); endorsements by Railway Labor's Political League for the general election (1948); Congressional voting records (1946-1949); and Senate speeches on labor by Hubert H. Humphrey (1949).
  - Anti-Labor Bills (1947) LMRA (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Report - U.S. Department of Labor (1948-49) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - H.R. 2536 (1946) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Railway Labor's Political League (1948-50) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - UN - Dumbarton Oaks (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Speech - National Labor Policy (1949) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 1-9. National Railroad Adjustment Board.
  Materials on the National Railroad Adjustment Board (1937-1950) include letters regarding international highway forwarders (1941) (trucks to be used in international service with all the bonding privileges accorded railroads); letters in opposition to a bill to construct and operate a belt conveyer between various points in Ohio; and letters regarding S.150/HR.628 reducing total freight revenues for railroads in the transport of coal and iron; minutes of a meeting called to organize a joint committee of railroad management and employees in Michigan for legislative purposes (1939) and minutes of the joint council of the Michigan railroad industry (1939); also a resolution outlining basic requirements of public policy bearing upon the relationship between competing forms of transportation.
  - NRAB - Awards, Third Division (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Awards - 1949-50 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agreement - Canadian Representative of U.S. NRAB (1934 - 35) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1-10. Business Competition with Other Industries.
  - Michigan Legislation on Trucking Activities (1939 - 41) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Coordinated Shipments (1949) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beit Conveyor (1949-51) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Mail (1948) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Public Policy - Competing Forms of Transportation (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - St. Lawrence Seaway (1949 + 1952) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 1-11. Railing Protection on Signals.
  - Colorlight Signal Poles (1951) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bracket Poles (1950-1957) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Floodlight Poles (1940-42) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1-12. Strike Charges/Reinstatements.
  Materials on strikes and reinstatements (1940-1958) include letters on signalmen positions abolished due to conditions arising from the locomotive firemen's strike, with a protest to the Railroad Retirement Board regarding the method of filing applications and allowing unemployment compensation during the strike; memorandum of understanding (1950) between the Brotherhood and the Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad, and the Lake Erie and Eastern Railroad in connection with restoration of small forces with revised operating rules upon the termination of the strike of conductors and trainmen on these properties; minutes (with by-laws) of the meeting of the Association of General Chairmen, Standard Labor Organizations on the New York Central System (1957); a paper supporting enactment of state legislation providing for the protection of employees adversely affected by the abandonment of railroad facilities; and letters regarding questions concerning work stoppages called by another craft or crafts.
  - Strike Payments (1950-51) Michigan Central Railroad (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Pittsburgh, Lake Erie/Lake Erie and Eastern Railroad Co. Strike (1950) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Layoffs - Indian Harbor Belt (1951) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Operating rules (1957-58) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Local Chairmen, Western System Lines (1952) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Signal Force (1951-55) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1-17. Interlocking Installations.
  - Interlocking joints (Diagrams) 1949-1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad Co. /State Line Interlocker (1945-50) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Walnut St. Nickel Plate Railroad (1950) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ridgeway, Ohio (1950) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Crestline Plant (1945) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Cincinnati and Ohio/Delaware Interlocking (1947) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Calumet Park (1949) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Oakland City, Indiana (1949) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Fostoria, Ohio (1946-48) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Union Switch and Signal Com. /Huff Interlocking (1947) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Nickel Plate Railroad/St. Mary's Interlocking (1947) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Signal Apparatus/Inspection of Foreign Lines (1946) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Grand Trunk West/Milawaukee Junction Interlocking (1947} (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Wayne Interlocking Plant (1951) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Columbus Union Depot (.1951-53) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Granite City (1952) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Warren, Pa. Automatic Gates (1952-53) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - G.M.O. /Alton, Illinois (1952-53) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Greenville, Ohio /Baltimore and Ohio Railroad (1952-55) Inoperative Distant Signals (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Miami Crossing, Ohio (1953) Cab Signals (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Preston Interlocking/Terre Haute, Indiana (1953) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Wapakoneta, Ohio/Baltimore and Ohio (1953) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Big Four/Jackson Street, Danville Illinois (1954 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Target Signal at Slater, Ohio/D.T.I. (1954 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Pelton Interlocking/Ontario, Canada (1954) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Ames Interlocking/Crawfordsville, Indiana (1953-50) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Franklin, Pa. (1954) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bridge over Cuyahoga River, Cleveland (1957) Diagrams; agreements (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Streator, Illinois (1956-57) Flashing H. Signals/Crossing Belts (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Toledo Terminal Railroad Tracks - Vulcan, Ohio (1954) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - East Alton and Bridge Junction (1957) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Big Four Signal Forces/Danville, Illinois (1954) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Kent Interlocking at Marion, Indiana (1957) (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Michigan Interlocking at Elkhart-Jackson Subdivision (1958) Diagram (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Flashers at Meridian St./Ohio Division (1962) (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Armitage, Ohio (1962) (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - D.T.I./ Adrian, Michigan (1962) (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Dunkirk Interlocking at Dunkirk, Ohio (1962) (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Grayville, Illinois Interlocking (1960-61) (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Pana, Illinois - Signals (1960) (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Oldsmobile Co./Cowle St., Lansing, Michigan (1958) (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Tates Point, Ohio (1963) (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Dean Interlocking (1963) (Box 1, Folder 50)
- 2-1. Motor Cars.
  Transcripts of investigations to determine cause and responsibility for accidental damage to motor cars (1951).
  - Legislative Cases in Ohio (Public Utilities Commission) 1952-54 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Motor Car Rules (1947) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Motor Car Rules (1939 - 1951) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Use of Snow Flangers (1949) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Elimination of Motor Car Set-Offs (1953) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Motor Car Repair (1953) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Complaints (Dispatcher/Operators) 1944-45 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Motor Car (Protection for Operation of) 1954 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Motor Car "Tops" (1952-53) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Article: "Safe Track Ahead" 1955-56 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Accidents Involving Motor Cars (1954-55) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Complaint (1950) New York Central System (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Accident (1950) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Accident (1949) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Case (Accident) 1940 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Accident Investigation (6/8/41) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Case of N.J. Burke (1936) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Compensation Case (G.F. Neil) 1941 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Minutes of Investigation (1949) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Settlement (pay) 1938 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Appeals for New Investigation (1944-49) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Investigation (1951) and Minutes (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Accident Report and Ensuing Correspondence (1951) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 2 (Collisions) Accident Convictions (1953-54) (Box 2, Folder 24)
- 2-2. Absence from Work.
  - Sick Leave (1955-56) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Leave of Absence (1958) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 2-5. Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad Signal Agreements.
  - Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad (1954-59) Agreements and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Belt Railway Company, Agreements and Correspondence (1954) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Maintenance Facilities (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Signal Work (1956) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Dolton Interlocking (1952-55) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ash Street Signal Work: Agreement (1956-57) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Interlocking BOCT/I.H.B. Diagrams and Correspondence (1950-52) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chicago Belt Railway (1951-54) (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 3-1. Administrative Business.
  - Labor-Management Reports, including correspondence (1960) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - General System Committee Minutes (1930-63) (lacks, 1931, 36, 38, 39, 41-43, 48, 61-62) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - By-laws; Revised 1949 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Affiliation of "Big 4" Signalmen Locals (1930) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - By-Laws amended (1956) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - General System Committee Reports (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 3-2. Finances.
  - Semi-Annual Report of Secretary-Treasurer (1930-62) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements of General Systems Committee (1933-51) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Grand Lodge Semi-Monthly Expense Report (1958-63) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Expense Account - R.L. Giant (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Meeting of General Chairmen - Minutes (1958-60) Association of General Chairman (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 3-3. Association of General Chairmen.
  - Demotion of J.M. Pattee (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Agenda Committee (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Addresses and Correspondence (1939-62) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Election of Vice Chairman (1957) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 3-4. Personal Papers, Receipts, and Correspondence.
  - War Time (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - I.R.S. 1950 Statements (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Federal Income Tax (1952-56, 1927-36) (Box 2, Folder 3)